A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 FA1472
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1988-2007; 1
  - Huntington Library, Art Collections, and Botanical Gardens - Reinterpretation of American Art Collection (American Collections Enhancements (ACE) Initiative, 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 228)
  - Huntington Library, Art Collections, and Botanical Gardens - Sabbatical for the Curator of American Art, 2001-2004 (Box 33, Folder 229)
  - Independent Teaching Project, Faculty of Color Program - Education Program, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 230)
  - Indiana University - Chinese Political Posters, 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 231)
  - Inner-City Scholarship Fund - Leadership Development Initiative Program, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 232-233)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art - General Support, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 234)
  - Institute of International Education - Elisabeth Luce Moore Leadership Program for Chinese Women, 1997-2003 (Box 34, Folder 235-236)
  - Institute of International Education - Elisabeth Luce Moore Leadership Program, 1994-2014 (Box 35, Folder 237-238)
  - Iliff School of Theology - New Curriculum for Globalization of Theological Education, 1991-2001 (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - In Trust, Inc. - Development and Fundraising, 1996-1998 (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - In Trust, Inc. - Luce Research Reports and Operating Expenses, 1999-2005 (Box 35, Folder 241)
  - Institute of East-West Studies - The Future of Security in the Asia-Eurasian Region, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 242)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, Crane-Rogers Foundation - Fellows Program, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 243)
  - Institute for Jewish, Christian, and Islamic Studies and Relations - Curriculum Test in Interfaith Values, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 244-245)
  - Institute for Student Achievement - Academic Enrichment Program for Junior High School Students, 1999-2003 (Box 36, Folder 246)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center - Institute of Church Administration and Management, 1999-2003 (Box 36, Folder 247)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center - General Operations, 2000-2004 (Box 36, Folder 248)
  - Interfaith Alliance Foundation - Seminary Outreach Conferences, 2000-2004 (Box 36, Folder 249)
  - International Center in New York - Citizenship Program, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 250)
  - International Center in New York - Expanding and Modernizing the Library, 2000-2004 (Box 37, Folder 251)
  - International Committee for the Peace Council - North Korean Delegation to Inter-Korea Reconciliation Seminar, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 252)
  - International Foundation for Art Research - 30th Anniversary Initiative, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 253)
  - International Partnership for Service Learning - Religious Studies and Community Service Program in the Philippines, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 254)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board - Doctoral Researchers Exchange with Mongolia, 1995-1998 (Box 37, Folder 255)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board - Mongolia Research Fellowship Program and Language Training Program for American Scholars, 1998-2003 (Box 37, Folder 256-257)
  - International Rescue Committee - Leo Cherne Library, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 258)
  - International Urban Associates - Transforming New York: Signs of Hope in the City, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 259)
  - Island Press/Center for Resource Economics - Environmental Instruction in Higher Education, 2001-2006 (Box 38, Folder 260-261)
  - Jewel Heart - Book Editor for Gelek Ripoche, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 262)
  - Jewish Museum - "Allegories: Paintings of Ben Shahn, 1943-1962" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 263)
  - Johns Hopkins University, National Foreign Language Center - Language Mission Project, 1995-1999 (Box 38, Folder 264)
  - Katonah Museum of Art - "Pavel Tchelitchew: Landscape of the Body" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 265)
  - Kent State University - Magaret Ratcliff Endowment Fund, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 266)
  - Learning Leaders - College Planning Program, 2000-2002 (Box 39, Folder 267)
  - The Learning Project, Inc. - Scholarships at the TLP Two School, 1999-2002 (Box 39, Folder 268)
  - The Learning Project, Inc. - Summer School Project, New York City, 1995-1997 (Box 39, Folder 269)
  - Lehman College Art Gallery - Public Art in the Bronx, 1995-2003 (Box 39, Folder 270)
  - Library of Congress - Center for the Book, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 271)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar for 106th Congress, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 272)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar for 107th Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 273)
  - The Living Pulpit - Managing Editor Compensation, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 274)
  - The Living Pulpit - Promoting Subscriptions to Seminarians, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 275)
  - Longhouse Foundation - Pilot Decorative Arts Classification System, 1996-2000 (Box 40, Folder 276-277)
  - Long Island Museum of American Art, History, and Carriages - The Tile Club, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 278)
  - Lontar Foundation - Translation of Indonesia Literature, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 279)
  - Clare Boothe Luce Policy Institute - "Issues for the Millenium" Conference, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 280)
  - Lycoming College - East/West Points of Contact, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 281)
  - Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church - "The Song of Being" (Pat Read), 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 282)
  - Madison Square Boys and Girls Clubs - Self Improvement Through Education (SITE), 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 283)
  - Marietta College - National Conferences on Leadership, 1998-2001 (Box 41, Folder 284)
  - McCormick Theological Seminary - Language Program, 1995-1999 (Box 41, Folder 285)
  - Maryland Historical Society - Baltimore City Life Museum Collection, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 286)
  - Mead Art Museum, Amherst College - Upgrade Collections Management (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1996-2000 (Box 41, Folder 287)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Swim Across America Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 288)
  - Mepkin Abbey - Clare Boothe Luce Library, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 289-290)
  - Metropolitan Athletics Congress, Inc. - MAC Attack Program, 1994-1999 (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - Micronesia Institute - Transitional Support, 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 292)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum - Decorative Arts Collection (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1998-2001 (Box 42, Folder 293-294)
  - Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth - "Arshile Gorky: The Breakthrough Years" Exhibition and Catalog, 1994-2001 (Box 42, Folder 295)
  - Montclair Art Museum - LeBrun Library Relocation and American Art Collection Accessibility, 2000-2002 (Box 43, Folder 296-297)
  - Montclair Art Museum - Northeast Art Museum Consortium, 1995-2001 (Box 43, Folder 298)
  - Montclair Art Museum - "Paris 1900: The American School at the Universal Exposition" and the LeBrun Library Automation and Expansion Project, 1997-2002 (Box 43, Folder 299-300)
  - Montclair Art Museum - "Precisionism in America, 1915-1941: Reordering Reality" Exhibition and Catalog, 1993-2001 (Box 44, Folder 301-302)
  - Mountain Institute - Peak Enterprise Program, 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 303)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute - 19th Century American Furniture (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1996-2001 (Box 44, Folder 304)
  - Museum of American Folk Art - From the Mind's Eye: American Self-Taught Artists, 1995-1999 (Box 44, Folder 305-306)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago - Archive of Art in Chicago, 1995-1999 (Box 44, Folder 307)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago - Chicago School of Painters, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 308)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, San Diego - Collection Accessibility Initiative (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1998-2003 (Box 45, Folder 309-310)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston - Martin Johnson Heade, 1996-2000 (Box 45, Folder 311-312)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Permanent Installation of the American Art Collection, 1999-2002 (Box 46, Folder 313-314)
  - Museum of Modern Art - Jackson Pollock Retrospective, 1997-1999 (Box 46, Folder 315-316)
  - Museum of Scotland and Heritage Trust Foundation - New Building, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 317)
  - Mystic Seaport Museum, Inc. - America and the Sea, 1996-1998 (Box 46, Folder 318)
  - National Academy of Design - "Rave Reviews: American Art and its Critics" Exhibition and Catalog, 1999-2001 (Box 47, Folder 319)
  - National Audubon Society - New York State Bird Areas Program, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 320)
  - National Center for Public Policy - "Missing Pages" Oral History Project, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 321)
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations - Public Education and Exchange Program, 1997-2001 (Box 47, Folder 322)
  - National Gallery of Art - Golden Age of Chinese Archaeology, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 323-324)
  - National Academy Museum and School of Fine Arts - Renovate Study Storage Facility and Collection Catalog, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 325-326)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts - "Amazons in the Drawing Room: The Art of Tomain Brooks" Exhibition and Catalog, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 327)
  - National Schools Committee for Economic Education, Inc. - "Economics: Playing for Real" Program, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 328)
  - National Theatre of the Deaf - Chinese Members to National Conference, 1994-1999 (Box 48, Folder 329)
  - Nativity Mission Center - After School and Weekend Tutorial Programs, 1998-2003 (Box 48, Folder 330)
  - Nativity Mission Center - Master Teacher Program, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 331)
  - Oakland Museum of California - Elmer Bischoff Exhibition and Catalog, 1999-2003 (Box 49, Folder 332-333)
  - Occidental College - Summer Project (1994), 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 334)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation, 1995-2000 (Box 49, Folder 335-336)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Museum - "O'Keeffe on Paper" Exhibition and Catalog, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 337)
  - Old Saybrook Historical Society - Martha Davis Soper Library, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 338)
  - Albert G. Oliver Program - Minority Recruitment Program, 1996-2002 (Box 49, Folder 339)
  - Opera Music Theatre International - 50th Anniversary Performance of Mephistopheles, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 340)
  - Orange County Museum of Art - San Francisco School of Abstract Expressionism, 1992-1997 (Box 50, Folder 341)
  - Overseas Development Council - United Nations Secretary-General Conference, 1998-2000 (Box 50, Folder 342)
  - Private Agencies Collaborating Together (PACT) - Vietnamese-American Volunteer Youth Project, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 343)
  - Palm Springs Desert Museum - Duane Hanson: Virtual Reality, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 344)
  - Parrish Art Museum - 10th Street, 1996-2001 (Box 50, Folder 345-346)
  - Partners for Livable Communities - Human Culture and Architectural Design, 1993-1999 (Box 50, Folder 347-348)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - Collection Research and Computerization (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1999-2003 (Box 51, Folder 349)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - Maxfield Parrish Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-1999 (Box 51, Folder 350)
  - Per Scholas - Computer Technician Training, 1998-2002 (Box 51, Folder 351-353)
  - Per Scholas - Job Training Program, 1996-2001 (Box 52, Folder 354-355)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Thomas Eakins, 1998-2002 (Box 52, Folder 356-357)
  - Philbrook Museum of Art - Native American Program, 1995-2000 (Box 52, Folder 358-359)
  - Phillips Academy, Andover - Institue for Recruitment of Teachers, 1998-2003 (Box 53, Folder 360-361)
  - Phipps Community Development Corporation - Pathway to State University of New York, Purchase, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 362)
  - Pittsburgh Theological Seminary - Metro-Urban Institute, 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 363-364)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Training of Teachers and Other Professionals Working with Teens, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 365)
  - Police Athletic League - Education Resource Program, 1995-2000 (Box 54, Folder 366)
  - Portland Art Museum - American Collection Installation and Research Project (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1999-2002 (Box 54, Folder 367)
  - Potomac Associates - United States-China Relations Opinion Poll, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 368)
  - Potomac Associates - United States-China Relations (Renewal), 1999-2001 (Box 54, Folder 369)
  - Pratt Institute - "Architectural Competitions in America" Exhibition, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 370)
  - Pratt Institute - "Pratt and its Gallery" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-2001 (Box 54, Folder 371)
  - Prep for Prep - Counselling Services for Disenfranchised Students, 1997-2000 (Box 55, Folder 372-373)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Dead Sea Scrolls Project, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 374)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Robert E. Speer Library Addition, 1988-1999 (Box 55, Folder 375)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Syriac Project with Dudley Cates and James Charlesworth, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 376)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Yalun Zhang, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 377)
  - Princeton University Press - Sargent's Triumph of Religion, Boston Library, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 378)
  - The Project on Religion and Human Rights - Study, 1994-1999 (Box 55, Folder 379)
  - Protestant Theological Faculty of Charles University, Prague - Ancient and Rare Books Collection, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 380-381)
  - Public Allies, New York - Academic Achievements of Developing Community Leaders, 2000-2003 (Box 56, Folder 382)
  - Public Conversations Project, 1998-2000 (Box 56, Folder 383)
  - Queens Museum of Art - "Tiffany: Behind the Glass" Exhibition and Brochure, 2000-2002 (Box 56, Folder 384)
  - Reading is Fundamental, 1996-2000 (Box 56, Folder 385)
  - Religion in American Life, 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 386-387)
  - Rheedlan Centers for Children and Families, Inc. - Saturday Academy Program in Central Harlem, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 388)
  - Riverside Church - Fosdick Convocation on Preaching and Worship, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 389)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Center - Kingdoms of Edward Hicks, 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 390-391)
  - Norman Rockwell Museum - "Norman Rockwell: Pictures for the American People" Touring Exhibition, 1998-2003 (Box 58, Folder 392-394)
  - St. John's University, Minnesota - Frank Kacmarcik Oral History on Video, 1996-1999 (Box 58, Folder 395-396)
  - St. Joseph Seminary - Pre-College Start-Up Program, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 397)
  - St. Joseph's College of Maine - Pilot Model of Collaboration with Diocese of Portland, 1999-2002 (Box 59, Folder 398)
  - St. Vincent's Services, Inc. - College Program, 1998-2003 (Box 59, Folder 399)
  - St. Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary - Library Development Expansion, 1996-1999 (Box 59, Folder 400)
  - Salvation Army of Greater New York - GAINS Program (Renewal), 1991-1999 (Box 59, Folder 401)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - "Carleton Watkins: The Art of Perception" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-1999 (Box 60, Folder 402-403)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - Sol Lewitt, 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 404-405)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - Eva Hesse Exhibtion and Catalog, 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 406-407)
  - School of American Research - Southwest Native American Art, 1999-2003 (Box 61, Folder 408-409)
  - School of American Research - Southwest Native American Art - CAC Presentation: Aesthetics and Accessibility (Box 61, Folder 408-409)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Seattle Art Museum - "Native Visions, Northwest Coast Art" Exhibition and Catalog, 1996-2000 (Box 61, Folder 410-411)
  - Seminary Consortium for Urban Pastoral Education (SCUPE), 1994-1999 (Box 61, Folder 412-413)
  - Senior Servies of Stamford - Over 60s Club New Common Room, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 414)
  - Seton Hall University - Graduate Program in Museum Professions, 1995-1998 (Box 62, Folder 415)
  - Seton Hall University - Scholarship for Museum Professions, 1998-2003 (Box 62, Folder 416)
  - Shelburne Museum - Archival Management Project, 1994-1999 (Box 62, Folder 417)
  - Shelburne Museum - American Folk Art Painting and Sculpture, 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 418)
  - Smith College - Enhance Public Awareness of American Art Collection, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 419)
  - Societas Liturgica - Travel Subsidies to 18th Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 63, Folder 420)
  - Soho Community Council - Exhibition at the Municipal Art Society, 1998-2001 (Box 63, Folder 421)
  - Southeast Center for Contemporary Art - Maya Lin, 1996-1999 (Box 63, Folder 422)
  - Springfield Library and Museums Association - American Art Collection Video Series, 1997-1999 (Box 63, Folder 423)
  - Stanford University - Asian Law Project, 1992-1999 (Box 63, Folder 424)
  - Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences - "The Angel in the Sun" (John LaFarge) Restoration, 2000-2001 (Box 63, Folder 425)
  - Student Conservation Association, Inc. - Conservation Career Development Program for College Students, 1999-2003 (Box 63, Folder 426)
  - Studio Museum, Harlem - Permanent Collection Research Project, 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 427)
  - Sustainable Development Institute - Atlantic CoastWatch Project, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 428)
  - Sheldon Swore Art Museum - Curator, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 429-430)
  - Tairona Heritage Trust - English Language Book on Kogi People, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 431)
  - Tate Gallery - "The American Sublime: Landscape Painting in America, 1820-1880" Exhibition and Catalog, 1998-2002 (Box 65, Folder 432-434)
  - Tate Gallery - "Barnett Newman" Exhibition and Catalog, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 435)
  - Teach for America - Transitional Support, 1995-1997 (Box 65, Folder 436-437)
  - Teach for America - Performance Assessment Policy Initative, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 438)
  - Telfair Museum of Art - Frederick Carl Frieseke Retrospective, 1999-2003 (Box 66, Folder 439-440)
  - Town School for Boys - New Teacher Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 66, Folder 441)
  - Trilateral Commission, 1992-1998 (Box 66, Folder 442-443)
  - Tufts University, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy - Program in Southeast Asian Studies, 1993-2001 (Box 67, Folder 444)
  - Tunhai University - Landscaping of Luce Chapel Grounds, 1999-2003 (Box 67, Folder 445)
  - Union Settlement Association - Youth with Promise Program, 1996-1999 (Box 67, Folder 446-447)
  - United Negro College Fund - Chinese Studies Program, 1994-2003 (Box 67, Folder 448-449)
  - University at Albany, State University of New York - Asian Studies Program, 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 450)
  - University Art Museum, University of California, Berkeley - Joan Brown Exhibition, 1996-1999 (Box 68, Folder 451)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Inter-University Board for Chinese Language Studies, 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 452)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Catalog of China Civil Service Collection, 1992-2000 (Box 68, Folder 453)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Consultation on Spirituality, 1997-1998 (Box 68, Folder 454)
  - University of Cambridge - Theology through the Arts Program, 1997-1999 (Box 68, Folder 455)
  - University of Delaware - Albert Pinkham Ryder Archive, 1989-1999 (Box 68, Folder 456)
  - University of Denver - American Studies Program in Vietnam, 1996-2000 (Box 69, Folder 457)
  - University of Maryland, College Park - Art History and Visual Culture of American Christianity, 1995-1999 (Box 69, Folder 458)
  - Urban Collaborative Accelerated Program (UCAP), 1995-1999 (Box 69, Folder 459)
  - University of Massachusetts - Robert L. Wood Visiting Professorship in Public and Urban Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 460)
  - University of Nebraska - Shape of Secular Religion Symposium, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 461)
  - University of San Fransisco, Ricci Institute - Conference of Chinese Scholars of Christianity, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 462)
  - University of South Carolina Press - Richard Mandell Book on Mepkin Abbey, 1996-1999 (Box 69, Folder 463)
  - University Settlement Society of New York - Talent Search Program, 1998-2002 (Box 69, Folder 464)
  - University of Washington - Advanced Study of Thai, Chiang Mai University, 1996-1998 (Box 69, Folder 465)
  - Volunteer Consulting Group, Inc. - Strengthening Boards of Non-Profits, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 466)
  - Walker Art Center - Frank Stella at Tyler Graphics, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 467)
  - Warner House - 18th Century Hangings and Liners, 1997-2001 (Box 70, Folder 468)
  - Washington Center - Internships for Appalachian Students, 1997-2000 (Box 70, Folder 469)
  - Washington Center - National Honor Scholarship Program for Minorities, 2000-2003 (Box 70, Folder 470)
  - White House Endowment Fund - Public Rooms of the White House, 1992-1998 (Box 70, Folder 471)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Edward Steichen, 1998-2001 (Box 70, Folder 472)
  - Wichita Art Museum - American Art Collection Catalog and Exhibition (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1996-2000 (Box 70, Folder 473-474)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society - Conservation Education Program in China, 1996-1998 (Box 71, Folder 475)
  - Winterthur Museum - Decorative Arts Photographic Collection and Index, 1998-2001 (Box 71, Folder 476)
  - Worcester Art Museum - Electronically Enhance Collection Accessibility, 1996-2002 (Box 71, Folder 477)
  - Wordsworth Trust - Feasibility Study of Properties and Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 478)
  - World Monuments Fund - International Center for Khmer Studies in China, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 479)
  - Worldteach, Inc. - China Teachers Consortium's Workshops, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 480)
  - Yale Divinity School - Abe Malherbe Scholarship Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 71, Folder 481)
  - Yale Divinity School - Conference on Vatican-Lutheran Agreement, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 482)
  - Yale University - Works of Jonathan Edwards, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 483)
  - Yale University - Henry R. Luce Center for International and Area Studies, 1990-1999 (Box 72, Folder 484-485)
  - Yale University Press Clippings - Henry R. Luce Center for International and Area Studies, 1991-1995 (Box 72, Folder 486)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - Collection of Miniatures, 1991-2001 (Box 72, Folder 487-488)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - Digitization of American Art Collection, 1997-2003 (Box 73, Folder 489-490)
  - Yellowstone Art Museum - Poindexter Collections, 1999-2002 (Box 73, Folder 491-492)
  - Yenching Graduate Institute - Yenching Journal of Chinese Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 73, Folder 493)
  - YMCA of Greater New York - St. Mary's Teen Center, 1996-2000 (Box 73, Folder 464)
  - YMCA of Greater New York - Chelsea Vibes Program, 1999-2003 (Box 73, Folder 495)
  - YWCA of the USA - Institute for Public Leadership, 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 496-497)
- Professorship Files, 1969-2001; 2
  - Occidental College, 1981-1994 (Box 74, Folder 498-501, Box 75, Folder 502-505)
  - Occidental Colllege (Renewal), 1988 (Box 75, Folder 506)
  - Princeton University, 1969-1977 (Box 75, Folder 507-508, Box 76, Folder 509-511)
  - Rice University, 1982-1985 (Box 76, Folder 512)
  - Rice University - Report, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 513)
  - Rice University (Renewal), 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 514)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1988-1993 (Box 77, Folder 515)
  - Sarah Lawrence College (Renewal), 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 516f)
  - Stanford University, 1990-1992 (Box 77, Folder 517-519)